allsitessorted.com 2012-10-28

# - Privacy Policy

Free Web Directory - All Sites Sorted » privacy 

### Privacy Policy:

These terms relate to this website and any affiliated or commonly owned or managed website that link here (referred to as this "site" or "website"). This site may collect information from users at several different points on our website. Submitting a comment, article, link, membership or user application or other information may require providing a valid e-mail address. However, we maintain a no-spam policy and if you submit a link, your e-mail address will not be sold or given to any third party. 

Registration is not required to use this website, but additional features may be available by doing so. During registration a user is required to give basic contact information (such as a user name and email address). This information is only used to provide password reminders should login information be forgotten, to send e-mails regarding the user's listing, provide e-mail updates or information or infrequently other promotions as deemed warranted.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about registration or use of this site, by the software running the site. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally information while on this site and is used to store page settings, provide usage information, access and/or login information. For example, by setting a cookie from our site, you may not have to enter a password more than once, thereby saving time while browsing. You are not required to accept cookies to use this site, although some features may not be available if you choose not to do so.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. This site offers access for all visitors. In order to participate in any way, users IP addresses are or may be recorded. This is designed to protect overall integrity and dissuade participants from harassing, spamming, flaming or other objectionable conduct. IP addresses may be stored to correspond to the submitter of a comment, link or other content on this site, and may be traced to an end user in cases of abuse. We also collect and analyze traffic data what search terms were used to visit our site. This allows us to optimize our website for the search engines and to understand what are users are interested in in order to better direct our website content. 

Aggregated demographic information may be shared with selected third party advertisers as proof of traffic volume and target audience for the purpose of securing advertising contracts on this site. The information is summarized and is in not linked to an individual visitor.

This web site contains links to other sites and/or articles or portions of articles from other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, content or other practices of such other sites and we do not review any such other sites for content, safety or accuracy. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

This site takes precautions to protect your information. The server on which this site resides is administered by a third party provider for whom we are not responsible, although we have found generally reliable. If you have any questions regarding the security at our website, you can send an email to the webmaster or may use the comments form.

Due to new rules applicable to websites, information websites that lead visitors to third party websites are required to disclose they may generate a commission through sales generated on all outgoing affiliate links. This site includes ads and/or other links for which a commission or fee may be generated. Commissions or other fees generated allow us to keep our website and network of websites online, provide relevant informative websites.

Changes of this statement will be posted to this page. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users well in advance with appropriate opt-out options. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. This site cannot be held responsible for notifying you of any changes made to this policy. This policy may change as the site develops and grows, so please re-visit this page as often as you wish.

Copyright © 2006-2010 All Sites Sorted. All rights reserved.
